{
  "question1": {
    "ans1": "Honeycomb Challenge",
    "ans2": "Tug of War",
    "ans3": "Glass Stepping Stones",
    "ans4": "Marbles",
    "question": "Which game involves players cutting shapes out of honeycomb without breaking them?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question2": {
    "ans1": "test",
    "ans2": "!start",
    "ans3": "idk",
    "ans4": "amogus",
    "question": "What was the first message ever inside Gamehall?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question3": {
    "ans1": "Mr.Oh",
    "ans2": "Mr.Kang",
    "ans3": "Mr.Lee",
    "ans4": "Mr.Cho",
    "question": "What is the name of the frontman in charge of the Squid Game?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question4": {
    "ans1": "test",
    "ans2": "!start",
    "ans3": "idk",
    "ans4": "amogus",
    "question": "What was the first message ever inside Gamehall?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question5": {
    "ans1": "<@841781116758261810>",
    "ans2": "<@1139406664584409159>",
    "ans3": "Immortal",
    "ans4": "<@493177799499055115>",
    "question": "Who is the owner of Squidsim?",
    "answer": 4,
    "comment": "4 == ZMN"
  },
  "question6": {
    "ans1": "Square",
    "ans2": "Triangle",
    "ans3": "Circle",
    "ans4": "Diamond",
    "question": "What is the iconic shape of the VIP's masks in Squid Game?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  "question7": {
    "ans1": "699",
    "ans2": "456",
    "ans3": "001",
    "ans4": "240",
    "question": "What is Gi-hun's number?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  "question8": {
    "ans1": "Lenny",
    "ans2": "Niko",
    "ans3": "ZMN",
    "ans4": "Cats",
    "question": "Who is the first top player?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  "question9": {
    "ans1": "Hae-soo",
    "ans2": "Seong-gi",
    "ans3": "Sang-woo",
    "ans4": "Gi-hun",
    "question": "Who is the main protagonist of Squid Game?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  "question10": {
    "ans1": "ZMN",
    "ans2": "Lenny",
    "ans3": "Conquestor",
    "ans4": "Immortal",
    "question": "Who is squidsims current top player?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  "question11": {
    "ans1": "Chirpy",
    "ans2": "Jerii",
    "ans3": "ZMN",
    "ans4": "Hecker",
    "question": "Who originally made squidsim trivia?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question12": {
    "ans1": "2021",
    "ans2": "2022",
    "ans3": "2023",
    "ans4": "2024",
    "question": "When was squidsim made?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question13": {
    "ans1": "Figurehead",
    "ans2": "VIP Leader",
    "ans3": "Mastermind",
    "ans4": "Front Man",
    "question": "What is the name of the masked figure who guides the players in Squid Game?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  "question14": {
    "ans1": "Abandoned Factory",
    "ans2": "Luxury Hotel",
    "ans3": "Underground Bunker",
    "ans4": "Amusement Park",
    "question": "What is the primary location for the Squid Game competition?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question15": {
    "ans1": "<@1089445042768334958>",
    "ans2": "<@898255050592366642>",
    "ans3": "<@1139406664584409159>",
    "ans4": "<@493177799499055115>",
    "question": "Who is the Lead Investigator?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question16": {
    "ans1": "<@493177799499055115>",
    "ans2": "<@1139406664584409159>",
    "ans3": "<@869658619103285289>",
    "ans4": "<@1089445042768334958>",
    "question": "Who is the first SQA?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  "question17": {
    "ans1": "November 15, 2024",
    "ans2": "January 5, 2025",
    "ans3": "September 27, 2024",
    "ans4": "December 26, 2024",
    "question": "When is squid game season 2 releasing?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  "question18": {
    "ans1": "<@978144382773518336>",
    "ans2": "<@1155116882135887903>",
    "ans3": "<@493177799499055115>",
    "ans4": "<@1202253257305489449>",
    "question": "Which person can make people into a cookie fairy?",
    "answer": 1
  },
  "question19": {
    "ans1": "ping",
    "ans2": "99!",
    "ans3": "!games",
    "ans4": "!rlgl",
    "question": "What was the first command executed on squidsim?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  "question20": {
    "ans1": "RH1N0",
    "ans2": "Golden Boy",
    "ans3": "Conquestor",
    "ans4": "Double",
    "question": "Who is the first Top Guard?",
    "answer": 2
  },
    "question21": {
    "ans1": "par0192",
    "ans2": "Chirpy",
    "ans3": "Bege",
    "ans4": "ZMN",
    "question": "Who is the first Head mod?",
    "answer": 1
  }
}
